[
  {
    "type": "instructions",
    "note": "Each question is followed by four options lettered A to D. Find the correct option for each question"
  },
  {
    "type": "quiz",
    "no": "1",
    "question": "In a class of 39 students, 25 offer Fante and 19 offer Twi. 5 students do not offer any of the two languages. How many students offer only twi?",
    "answer": "C",
    "options": {
      "A": "6",
      "B": "7",
      "C": "8",
      "D": "9"
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "quiz",
    "no": "2",
    "question": "Mary and Charity entered into a business partnership and agreed to share their profit in the ration 5:4 respectively. If Mary received GHC5,000.00 less than Charity, jow much profit did they make?",
    "answer": "D",
    "options": {
      "A": "GHC30,000.00",
      "B": "GHC35,000.00",
      "C": "GHC40,000.00",
      "D": "GHC45,000.00"
    }
  },{
    "type": "quiz",
    "no": "3",
    "question": "y varies inversely as the square of x. When x = 3, y = 100. Find the value of x when y = 25.",
    "answer": "B",
    "options": {
      "A": "x = 30",
      "B": "x = 12",
      "C": "x = 6",
      "D": "x = 5"
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "quiz",
    "no": "4",
    "question": "A chord of a circle with radius 5cm subtends an angle of 70 at the centre. Find, correct to one decimal place, the length of the chord.",
    "answer": "C",
    "options": {
      "A": "8.2cm",
      "B": "5.7cm",
      "C": "4.1cm",
      "D": "2.9cm"
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "quiz",
    "no": "5",
    "question": "Find the truth set of the equation: (x - 2)2 + 3 = (x + 1)2 -6",
    "answer": "C",
    "options": {
      "A": "{-2}",
      "B": "{-1}",
      "C": "{1}",
      "D": "{2}"
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "quiz",
    "no": "6",
    "question": "A pyramid with a square base has a volume of 1,400cm3. If a side of the base is 10cm long, find the height of the pyramid.",
    "answer": "C",
    "options": {
      "A": "70cm",
      "B": "42cm",
      "C": "21cm",
      "D": "7cm"
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "quiz",
    "no": "7",
    "question": "Whic of the following about parrallelograms are true?",
    "answer": "B",
    "options": {
      "A": "Opposite angles are supplementary.",
      "B": "Opposite angles are complementary.",
      "C": "Opposite angles are equal.",
      "D": "Opposite angles are reflex angles."
    }
  },{
    "type": "quiz",
    "no": "8",
    "question": "Calculate the distance between points (3, -2) and (8, 10) ",
    "answer": "C",
    "options": {
      "A": "12 units.",
      "B": "13 units.",
      "C": "14 units.",
      "D": "15 units."
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "quiz",
    "no": "9",
    "question": "Express the bearing of 312 in compass direction form.",
    "answer": "C",
    "options": {
      "A": "S 48 W",
      "B": "N 48 W",
      "C": "S 48 E",
      "D": "N 48 E"
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "quiz",
    "no": "10",
    "question": "An old man goes for a walk every 6 days. If he went for a walk on Wednesday, when will he go for his next walk? ",
    "answer": "B",
    "options": {
      "A": "Monday",
      "B": "Tuesday",
      "C": "Wednesday",
      "D": "Thursday"
    }

  }
]
